<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lordpedal RSS</title>
<link>https://lordpedal.gitlab.io</link>
<description>...la culminación de un fin es el comienzo de una realidad.</description>

            <item>
            <title>The Hacker News: New Exploit Bypasses Existing Spectre-V2 Mitigations in Intel, AMD, Arm CPUs</title>
            <link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/03/new-exploit-bypasses-existing-spectre.html</link>
            <description>New Exploit Bypasses Existing Spectre-V2 Mitigations in Intel, AMD, Arm CPUs</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:10:22 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>The Hacker News: Chinese APT41 Hackers Broke into at Least 6 U.S. State Governments: Mandiant</title>
            <link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/03/chinese-apt41-hackers-broke-into-at.html</link>
            <description>Chinese APT41 Hackers Broke into at Least 6 U.S. State Governments: Mandiant</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:09:59 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>The Hacker News: Here's How to Find if WhatsApp Web Code on Your Browser Has Been Hacked</title>
            <link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/03/heres-how-to-find-if-whatsapp-web-code.html</link>
            <description>Here's How to Find if WhatsApp Web Code on Your Browser Has Been Hacked</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:09:41 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>The Hacker News: Russian Pushing New State-run TLS Certificate Authority to Deal With Sanctions</title>
            <link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/03/russian-pushing-its-new-state-run-tls.html</link>
            <description>Russian Pushing New State-run TLS Certificate Authority to Deal With Sanctions</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:08:52 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Blog – Hackaday: Ice Fishing Tent Makes Winter Ham Radio Comfy</title>
            <link>https://hackaday.com/2022/03/12/ice-fishing-tent-makes-winter-ham-radio-comfy/</link>
            <description>Ice Fishing Tent Makes Winter Ham Radio Comfy</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:00:25 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Una al Día: Se filtran 190 GB del código fuente de los Samsung Galaxy</title>
            <link>https://unaaldia.hispasec.com/2022/03/se-filtran-190-gb-del-codigo-fuente-de-los-samsung-galaxy.html</link>
            <description>Se filtran 190 GB del código fuente de los Samsung Galaxy</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 06:00:00 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Desde Linux: Heroic Games Launcher: Lanzador nativo de juegos Epic Games y GOG</title>
            <link>https://blog.desdelinux.net/heroic-games-launcher/</link>
            <description>Heroic Games Launcher: Lanzador nativo de juegos Epic Games y GOG</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 05:00:18 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Blog – Hackaday: Retrotechtacular: Measuring TV Audiences with the “Poll-O-Meter”</title>
            <link>https://hackaday.com/2022/03/12/retrotechtacular-measuring-tv-audiences-with-the-poll-o-meter/</link>
            <description>Retrotechtacular: Measuring TV Audiences with the “Poll-O-Meter”</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 03:00:49 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Linux Adictos: Red Hat dice que hay mayor probabilidad que empresas elijan proveedores contribuyan a la comunidad open source</title>
            <link>https://www.linuxadictos.com/red-hat-dice-que-hay-mayor-probabilidad-que-empresas-elijan-proveedores-contribuyan-a-la-comunidad-open-source.html</link>
            <description>Red Hat dice que hay mayor probabilidad que empresas elijan proveedores contribuyan a la comunidad open source</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 00:50:04 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Blog – Hackaday: How To Make Laser-cut Decals On The Cheap</title>
            <link>https://hackaday.com/2022/03/12/how-to-make-laser-cut-decals-on-the-cheap/</link>
            <description>How To Make Laser-cut Decals On The Cheap</description>
            <pubDate>Sun Mar 13 00:00:00 2022</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Ubunlog: La nueva version de desarrollo de Wine 7.4 llega con cerca de 505 cambios</title>
            <link>https://ubunlog.com/la-nueva-version-de-desarrollo-de-wine-7-4-llega-con-cerca-de-505-cambios/</link>
            <description>La nueva version de desarrollo de Wine 7.4 llega con cerca de 505 cambios</description>
            <pubDate>Sat Mar 12 23:48:50 2022</pubDate>
            </item></channel>
</rss>