<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lordpedal RSS</title>
<link>https://lordpedal.gitlab.io</link>
<description>...la culminación de un fin es el comienzo de una realidad.</description>

            <item>
            <title>Engadget: The Google Play video app will leave Roku, Vizio, LG and Samsung's TV platforms</title>
            <link>https://www.engadget.com/google-play-movies-tv-june-15-214454191.html</link>
            <description>The Google Play video app will leave Roku, Vizio, LG and Samsung's TV platforms</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:44:54 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Xataka: Consiguen por primera vez extender la vida de un satélite en su órbita geosíncrona acoplando otro satélite que haga de propulsor</title>
            <link>http://feeds.weblogssl.com/~r/xataka2/~3/rY2E8Jlaqzg/consiguen-primera-vez-extender-vida-satelite-su-orbita-geosincrona-acoplando-otro-satelite-que-haga-propulsor</link>
            <description>Consiguen por primera vez extender la vida de un satélite en su órbita geosíncrona acoplando otro satélite que haga de propulsor</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:43:42 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Guías | Digital Trends Español: Te explicamos cómo instalar fuentes en Windows 10</title>
            <link>https://es.digitaltrends.com/computadoras/instalar-fuentes-en-windows-10/</link>
            <description>Te explicamos cómo instalar fuentes en Windows 10</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:30:49 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Lifehacker: Ask Your Prospective Landlord These Questions, Because Otherwise They Won't Tell You</title>
            <link>https://lifehacker.com/ask-your-prospective-landlord-these-questions-because-1846668507</link>
            <description>Ask Your Prospective Landlord These Questions, Because Otherwise They Won't Tell You</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:30:00 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Make: DIY Projects and Ideas for Makers: Plan CO2: Montreal Dad Makes a CO2 Monitor for His Daughter’s Classroom</title>
            <link>https://makezine.com/2021/04/12/plan-co2-montreal-dad-makes-a-co2-monitor-for-his-daughters-classroom/</link>
            <description>Plan CO2: Montreal Dad Makes a CO2 Monitor for His Daughter’s Classroom</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:11:06 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Wwwhat's new?: Microsoft adquiere Nuance para reforzar sus servicios de atención médica desde la nube</title>
            <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/WwwhatsNew/~3/mPdsdCIYo54/</link>
            <description>Microsoft adquiere Nuance para reforzar sus servicios de atención médica desde la nube</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:00:21 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Lifehacker: Are the Hooks on Your Squat Rack Too High?</title>
            <link>https://vitals.lifehacker.com/are-the-hooks-on-your-squat-rack-too-high-1846668383</link>
            <description>Are the Hooks on Your Squat Rack Too High?</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 21:00:00 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Computación | Digital Trends Español: Nvidia planta cara a Intel con su nuevo procesador Grace</title>
            <link>https://es.digitaltrends.com/computadoras/nvidia-grace-procesador-centros-de-datos-competencia-intel/</link>
            <description>Nvidia planta cara a Intel con su nuevo procesador Grace</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 20:59:36 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Lifehacker: The Different Grades of Beef and What They Mean</title>
            <link>https://skillet.lifehacker.com/the-different-grades-of-beef-and-what-they-mean-1846667553</link>
            <description>The Different Grades of Beef and What They Mean</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 20:45:00 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Engadget: Intel wants to make chips for automakers to help with the global shortage</title>
            <link>https://www.engadget.com/intel-car-chip-plan-203020766.html</link>
            <description>Intel wants to make chips for automakers to help with the global shortage</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 20:30:20 2021</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
            <title>Lifehacker: 27 Movies to Stream When You Need a Good Cry</title>
            <link>https://lifehacker.com/27-movies-to-stream-when-you-need-a-good-cry-1846667857</link>
            <description>27 Movies to Stream When You Need a Good Cry</description>
            <pubDate>Mon Apr 12 20:30:00 2021</pubDate>
            </item></channel>
</rss>